Register of the Stanislaw Mikolajczyk Papers, 1899-1966
Hoover Institution Archives
- GOVERNMENT SERVICE FILE, 1940-1946
  - Ministerstwo Spraw Zagranicznych (Ministry of Foreign Affairs)
    - Poland. Ambasada (Soviet Union)
      - Dzial Opieki Spolecznej (Department of Social Welfare)
        - General
          - Reports
            - General
              - 1941
                - September-December (Folder 31)
                - October (Folder 32)
              - 1942 January-July (Folder 33)
            - Conditions of Polish citizens (Box 43, Folder 1)
            - Inmates, 1941 September-November (Folder 2)
            - Liaison officers, 1941 (Folder 3)
            - Polish Lithuanian relations, 1942 (Folder 4)
            - Statistics on number of deportees, 1939-1941 (Folder 5)
        - Dzial Transportowy (Transport Department), 1942 March-April (Folder 6)
      - Kot, Stanislaw. Materials, reports, correspondence destined for Wladyslaw Sikorski
        - General
          - 1941 October-November (Folder 7)
          - 1942 January-April (Folder 8)
        - Dispatches
          - 1941 September-December (Folder 9)
          - 1942
            - January-March (Folder 10)
            - April-May (Folder 11)
            - June-August (Folder 12)
            - September-December (Folder 13)
          - 1943 January-February (Folder 14)
    - Soviet occupation zone of Poland, 1940-1941
      - General
        - Bulletin (Folder 15)
        - Reports
          - General (Folder 16)
          - Czapski, Jozef, 1941. Holograph (Folder 17)
          - Kisielewski, J., 1940 (Folder 18)
          - Tyszynski, Henryk, "Rzady sowieckie w Wilnie czerwiec 1940-luty 1941: Szkic sprawozdawczy," 1941. Typescript (Folder 19)
      - Lwow region
        - General
          - General (Folder 20)
          - Correspondence (Folder 21)
        - Academic and intellectual circles (Folder 22)
        - Ethnic minorities (Folder 23)
        - Khrushchev's and Ponomarenko's implementation of Soviet policies in the region (Folder 24)
        - Peasants (Folder 25)
      - Wilno region
        - General (Folder 26)
        - Deportations and imprisonment (Folder 27)
        - Ethnic minorities (Folder 28)
  - Ministerstwo Sprawiedliwosci (Ministry of Justice) - Constitutional Amendment, Paragraph 79, 1941 (Folder 29)
  - Naczelna Izba Kontroli (Comptroller's Office). Reports
    - 1939 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1940
      - January-June (Folder 2)
      - January-December (Folder 3)
  - Naczelny Wodz Sil Zbrojnych, Sztab Naczelnego Wodza
    - General (General Staff)
      - 1943
        - February-August (Folder 4)
        - September-October (Folder 5)
        - November-December (Folder 6)
      - 1944
        - January-March (Folder 7)
        - April-June (Folder 8)
        - July-September. Includes report on V-2 (Folder 9)
        - October-December (Folder 10)
    - Communiqués
      - 1940 January (Folder 11)
      - 1941
        - February (Folder 12)
        - October (Folder 13)
    - Dispatches from Poland, 1945
      - January-April (Folder 14)
      - May
        - General (Folder 15)
        - Naczelne Sily Zbrojne (Folder 16)
      - June (Folder 17)
    - Reports - "Dzialalnosc oddzialow AK na ziemiach krakowskich," n.d. Typescript (Folder 18)
  - Premier [Prime Minister]. See also Wicepremier
    - General
      - General
        - 1940 (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - 1941 (Folder 2)
        - 1942
          - September-October. Includes material related to reform in Polish Armed Forces (Folder 3)
          - November-December (Folder 4)
        - 1943
          - January (Folder 5)
          - February (Folder 6)
          - March (Folder 7)
          - April (Folder 8)
          - May (Folder 9)
          - July (Folder 10)
          - August (Folder 11)
          - September (Folder 12)
          - October (Folder 13)
          - November (Folder 14)
          - December (Folder 15)
        - 1944
          - January (Box 46, Folder 1)
          - February (Folder 2)
          - March (Folder 3)
          - April (Folder 4)
          - May (Folder 5)
          - June (Folder 6)
          - July (Folder 7)
          - August (Folder 8)
          - September (Box 47, Folder 1)
          - October (Folder 2)
          - November
            - 1-19 (Folder 3)
            - 20-30 (Folder 4)
      - Army, Situation in, 1940 (Folder 5)
      - Benes, Edvard, 1943-1944 (Folder 6)
      - Burza Plan
        - General, 1943-1944 (Folder 7)
        - Instructions for Poland, 1943 October (Folder 8)
        - Uprising, Preparations for, 1943 (Folder 9)
      - Emissaries
        - Celt, Marek (Folder 10)
        - Suitcases and belts delivered to Poland. Receipts, 1944 July (Folder 11)
      - French campaign, 1940 June (Folder 12)
      - Gaulle, Charles de, 1943 December (Folder 13)
      - Government crisis
        - 1940 July (Folder 14)
        - 1943 July
          - List (Folder 15)
          - Enclosures
            - General
              - A-G (Folder 16)
              - H-J (Folder 17)
            - Nos. 1-30 (Folder 18)
          - Reports - "Przebieg kryzysu rzadowego po smierci Gen. Sikorskiego, 5-15 lipca, 1943." Typescript (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - 1945
          - General (Folder 2)
          - Memoranda (Folder 3)
          - Transcripts of Mikolajczyk's talks with Allan, Anders, Arciszewski, Cadogan, Churchill, Eden, Harriman, Jagodzinski, Popiel, Sargent, Schoenfeld, Stanczyk, Warner
            - January-March (Folder 4)
            - April-June (Folder 5)
      - Government members, 1943 April (Folder 6)
      - Government restructuring, 1944
        - General
          - January-March (Folder 7)
          - May-June (Folder 8)
          - July-August (Folder 9)
          - September-October (Folder 10)
          - December. Includes correspondence following Mikolajczyk's resignation (Folder 11)
        - Dispatches
          - 1943 (Folder 12)
          - 1944
            - General (Folder 13)
            - Political parties (Folder 14)
            - Komitet Do Spraw Kraju - Polish-Soviet relations, October-November (Folder 15)
        - Publications - Listy z Londynu, August-November (Folder 16)
      - Ministers, Responsibilities of, 1943 (Folder 17)
      - Moscow trips. Includes papers of Deputy Prime Ministers
        - Sikorski, Wladyslaw (1939-1943). Material relating to the agreement with the Soviet Union of 1941
          - Communiqués (Box 49, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence. Includes a letter from Ivan Maisky, Soviet Embassy in London, 1941 August 5, regarding in particular the appointment of Wladyslaw Anders (Folder 2)
          - Drafts
            - British (Folder 3)
            - Polish (Folder 4)
            - Soviet (Folder 5)
          - Final text
            - General (Folder 6)
            - Enclosures
              - 1-10 (Folder 7)
              - 11-19 (Folder 8)
          - Interviews - Anders, Wladyslaw (Folder 9)
          - Minutes - Rada Ministrow, 1941 July 25 (Folder 10)
          - Notes (Folder 11)
          - Press, British (Folder 12)
          - Speeches - Sikorski, Wladyslaw (Folder 13)
          - Talk transcripts
            - British officials (Folder 14)
            - Soviet officials (Folder 15)
          - Translations, English (Folder 16)
        - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw (1943-1945)
          - First, 1944 August
            - Correspondence (Folder 17)
            - Dispatches on Warsaw Uprising of 1944 (Folder 18)
            - Notes
              - General (Folder 19)
              - Personal (Folder 20)
            - Reports - Rada Narodowa, August 14 (Folder 21)
            - Transcripts of talks
              - Molotov and Stalin (Folder 22)
              - Preliminary
                - General (Folder 23)
                - Grabski, 1944 June (Folder 24)
          - Second, 1944 October
            - Agreement, October 16
              - General (Box 50, Folder 1)
              - Drafts (Folder 2)
            - Correspondence - Harriman, William Averell (Folder 3)
            - Dispatches (Folder 4)
            - Notes (Folder 5)
            - Press file
              - General (Folder 6)
              - Polish (Folder 7)
            - Reports
              - General (Folder 8)
              - Rada Narodowa, October 27 (Folder 9)
              - Tabor, General - Incident (Folder 10)
            - Transcripts of talks (Folder 11)
          - Third (as Deputy Prime Minister), 1945 June. Includes materials on preparations for Moscow talks on general subjects as well as on Rada Jednosci Narodowej (Council of National Unity) and Tymczasowy Rzad Jednosci Narodowej (Provisional Government of National Unity)
            - General (Folder 12)
            - Agreement, June 24 (Folder 13)
            - Appeal, July 1 (Folder 14)
            - Correspondence (Folder 15)
            - List of government members (Folder 16)
            - Notes
              - Acknowledging creation of new government, June-July (Folder 17)
              - Personal (Folder 18)
            - Press file
              - Bulletins (Folder 19)
              - Excerpts of articles by Foreign Office, June 18-23 (Folder 20)
            - Talk transcripts, including of Commission of Three (Folder 21)
            - Telegrams (Folder 22)
          - Fourth (as Deputy Prime Minister), 1945 August 6-17
            - General
              - Border, Agreement on (Folder 23)
              - War reparations
                - General (Folder 24)
                - Agreement (Folder 25)
                - Talks (Folder 26)
            - Clippings (Folder 27)
            - Diary of Stanislaw Mikolajczyk (Folder 28)
            - Itinerary (Folder 29)
            - Notes
              - August 13 (Folder 30)
              - August 16 (Folder 31)
            - Visa (Folder 32)
      - Polish-British military agreement, 1940 (Folder 33)
      - Polish-Czechoslovak relations, 1940 (Folder 34)
      - Polish-Soviet agreement, 1941 July. Enclosure no. 16. Typescript (Folder 35)
      - Post-war plans
        - Central European Federation - Litauer, Mieczyslaw, 1942 (Folder 36)
        - Professional associations in Great Britain, 1943-1944 (Folder 37)
        - Social system - "Zasady przyszlego ustroju panstwowego Polski opracowane przez Komisje Spraw Ustrojowych przy Prezesie Rady Ministrow." Typescript (Folder 38)
      - Rada Obrony Narodowej (Folder 39)
      - Talks
        - Allies, 1940-1941 (Folder 40)
        - Churchill, Winston, 1942 March (Folder 41)
      - Warsaw Uprising, 1944
        - General
          - General (Folder 42)
          - Communiqués (Folder 43)
          - Correspondence (Folder 44)
          - Declarations (Folder 45)
          - Office journal, July 26 - October 18 (Folder 46)
          - Press clippings (Folder 47)
          - Radio dispatches, 1944
            - Copies
              - July (Folder 48)
              - August (Folder 49)
              - September (Folder 50)
              - October (Folder 51)
              - November (Folder 52)
            - Originals
              - August (Box 51, Folder 1)
              - September (Folder 2)
              - October (Folder 3)
          - Speeches (Folder 4)
          - Telegrams, July 27-August 4 (Folder 5)
        - Burza Plan (Folder 6)
        - Deportations from Warsaw, 1944 October-November (Folder 7)
        - Naczelny Wodz (Folder 8)
        - Rada Narodowa
          - General (Folder 9)
          - Post-uprising plans (Folder 10)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - 1939 (Folder 11)
        - 1941
          - January-February
            - General (Folder 12)
            - Kot, Stanislaw, to Wladyslaw Sikorski, on Polish Underground and on Sosnkowski's report (Folder 13)
          - March (Folder 14)
          - April-June (Folder 15)
          - July
            - General (Folder 16)
            - Eden, Anthony (Folder 17)
          - August-September
            - General (Folder 18)
            - Reorganization of General Staff (Folder 19)
          - October-December (Folder 20)
        - 1942
          - January-June (Folder 21)
          - July-August (Folder 22)
          - September-October (Folder 23)
          - November-December (Folder 24)
        - 1943
          - General
            - January-February (Folder 25)
            - March-April (Folder 26)
            - May-June (Folder 27)
          - Intelligence Department (Folder 28)
      - Radio dispatches
        - General
          - 1943
            - January-June (Box 52, Folder 1)
            - July-December (Folder 2)
          - 1944
            - January-November (Folder 3)
            - December (Folder 4)
          - 1945
            - January (Folder 5)
            - February-March (Folder 6)
            - April-May (Folder 7)
        - Arciszewski's Government
          - General, 1945
            - January (Folder 8)
            - March (Folder 9)
            - April (Folder 10)
          - "Rzad Arciszewskiego w swietle depesz krajowych"
            - 1944 (Folder 11)
            - 1945 (Folder 12)
          - "Zbior korespondencji zebranej przez Stanislawa Mikolajczyka"
            - A, 1944 December-1945 April (Folder 13)
            - B, 1944 December-1945 May (Folder 14)
        - Trojkat
          - 1943
            - January-March (Folder 15)
            - April-June (Folder 16)
            - July-September (Folder 17)
            - October-December (Folder 18)
          - 1944 January-November (Folder 19)
      - Sosnkowski, Kazimierz, 1940 (Folder 20)
      - Zaborowski, W., 1943 April (Folder 21)
    - Documents (in order arranged by Stanislaw Mikolajczyk)
      - Komisja Parlamentarna Brytyjsko-Polska w Izbie Gmin (Polish-British Parliamentary Commission in the House of Commons), 1943 December 9
        - Index (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Nos. 1-9 (Folder 2)
        - Nos. 10-16 (Folder 3)
      - Polsko-sowieckie stosunki (Polish-Soviet relations), 1943-1944
        - Index (Folder 4)
        - Nos. 1-10 (Folder 5)
        - Nos. 11-20 (Folder 6)
        - Nos. 21-30 (Folder 7)
        - Nos. 31-40 (Folder 8)
        - Nos. 41-47 (Folder 9)
      - Przesilenie 24-29 listopad 1944 (Government crisis) 1944 November 24-29
        - Index (Folder 10)
        - Nos. 1-19 (Folder 11)
        - Nos. 21-40 (Folder 12)
        - Nos. 41-54 (Folder 13)
      - Rozmowy E i RWB (Talks between E and RWB), n.d.
        - Subject index (Folder 14-15)
      - Rozmowy E (Talks with E), 1943-1944
        - Index (Folder 16)
        - Nos. I-II (Folder 17)
        - Nos. 1-20 (Folder 18)
        - Nos. 21-39 (Folder 19)
        - Nos. 40-59 (Folder 20)
        - Nos. 60-69 (Folder 21)
      - Rozmowy RWB (Talks with RWB), 1943-1945
        - Index (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - Nos. 1-20 (Folder 2)
        - Nos. 21-39 (Folder 3)
        - Nos. 40-59 (Folder 4)
        - Nos. 60-61 (Folder 5)
        - Nos. 62-71 (Folder 6)
        - Nos. 72-86 (Folder 7)
        - Nos. 87-109 (Folder 8)
        - Nos. 110-120 (Folder 9)
        - Nos. 121-131 (Folder 10)
        - Nos. 132-144 (Folder 11)
        - Nos. 145-152 (Folder 12)
        - Nos. 156-179 (Folder 13)
        - Nos. 180-199 (Folder 14)
        - Nos. 200-220 (Folder 15)
        - Nos. 221-239 (Folder 16)
        - Nos. 240-261 (Folder 17)
        - Nos. 262-279 (Folder 18)
        - Nos. 280-290 (Box 55, Folder 1)
        - Nos. 291-310 (Folder 2)
        - Nos. 311-330 (Folder 3)
        - Nos. 331-350 (Folder 4)
        - Nos. 351-359 (Folder 5)
        - Nos. 361-379 (Folder 6)
        - Nos. 381-400 (Folder 7)
        - Nos. 401-413 (Folder 8)
      - Rozmowy T.J. (Talks with T.J.), 1941-1942, 1944
        - Index (Folder 9)
        - Nos. 1-36 (Folder 10)
        - Nos. 36-76 (Folder 11)
    - Interviews, 1944 (Folder 12)
    - Private dossier, 1940-1944
      - Index (Folder 13)
      - Nos. 1-60 (Folder 14)
      - Nos. 61-120 (Folder 15)
      - Nos. 121-179 (Folder 16)
      - Nos. 180-266 (Folder 17)
    - Reports
      - General, 1943 July-August (Folder 18)
      - Administrative division of German-occupied Poland, 1943 October (Folder 19)
      - Airplane accidents
        - Flight to Canada - Bomb incident. Investigation report, 1942 March-April (Folder 20)
        - Montreal, 1942 November 31 (Folder 21)
      - Armia Krajowa, 1943-1944 (Folder 22)
      - Auschwitz, 1944 November-December (Folder 23)
      - Palestine, 1943 (Folder 24)
      - Polish diplomatic outposts in Hungary and Romania, Anti-government circles in. Typescript, 1940 May (Folder 25)
      - Political parties in occupied Poland, 1942-1943 (Folder 26)
      - Press reviews
        - Foreign, 1945 February (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - Polish, 1943 December (Folder 2)
      - Transfer of dollars, 1944 (Folder 3)
    - Speeches
      - 1939 (Folder 4)
      - 1940 (Folder 5)
      - 1941
        - General (Folder 6)
        - Polish-Soviet agreement (Folder 7)
        - Rada Narodowa (Folder 8)
      - 1942
        - January-March (Folder 9)
        - April-June (Folder 10)
        - July-September (Folder 11)
        - October-December (Folder 12)
      - 1943
        - Index (Folder 13)
        - January-March, nos. 1-9 (Folder 14)
        - April-June, nos. 10-22 (Folder 15)
        - July-September, nos. 23-40 (Folder 16)
        - October-December, nos. 41-46 (Folder 17)
      - 1944
        - General (Folder 18)
        - Poland (Folder 19)
        - Rada Narodowa (Folder 20)
        - Soldiers (Folder 21)
    - Statements, 1944 (Folder 22)
  - Prezydent
    - General
      - 1939 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - 1940 (Folder 2)
      - 1941 (Folder 3)
      - 1942-1944 (Folder 4)
      - 1947 (Folder 5)
    - Bulletin issues, Sprawy Polskie, nos. 6-7, 1948 (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - 1939 (Folder 7)
      - 1940
        - Government crisis, July (Folder 8)
        - Possibility of Polish-Soviet rapprochement (Zaleski, August - Halifax, Edward F.) (Folder 9)
      - 1941 - Polish-Soviet Treaty
        - Opposition to the treaty (Folder 10)
        - Sikorski, Wladyslaw - Raczkiewicz, Wladyslaw (Folder 11)
      - 1942 (Folder 12)
      - 1943 (Folder 13)
      - 1944 (Folder 14)
    - Decrees, 1942-1944 (Folder 15)
    - Reports
      - Border crossing to Romania in 1939 by Roger Raczynski (Folder 16)
      - Sikorski's government after the fall of France (Folder 17)
    - Speeches
      - General, 1942-1944 (Folder 18)
      - Rada Narodowa, 1940 (Folder 19)
  - Rada Narodowa (National Council) [Acting President]
    - General
      - Minutes of sessions
        - 1940
          - February (Folder 20)
          - March (Folder 21)
          - April (Folder 22)
          - June
            - Angers (Folder 23)
            - Libourne (Folder 24)
          - July (Folder 25)
          - August (Folder 26)
          - October (Folder 27)
          - November (Box 58, Folder 1)
          - December (Folder 2)
        - 1941
          - February (Folder 3)
          - March (Folder 4)
          - April (Folder 5)
          - May (Folder 6)
          - June (Folder 7)
          - July (Folder 8)
      - Regulations
        - 1939 (Folder 9)
        - 1940 (Folder 10)
      - Reports
        - Volume 1, 1942 April-1943 January
          - List (Folder 11)
          - Nos. 1-107 (Folder 12)
          - Nos. 108-203 (Box 59, Folder 1)
          - Nos. 204-307 (Folder 2)
          - Nos. 308-417 (Folder 3)
          - Nos. 418-520 (Folder 4)
          - Nos. 521-628 (Folder 5)
          - Nos. 629-718 (Folder 6)
        - Volume 2, 1944
          - List (Folder 7)
          - Nos. 719-831 (Folder 8)
          - Nos. 832-923 (Folder 9)
          - Nos. 924-1008 (Folder 10)
          - Nos. 1009-1099 (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - Volume 3, 1944
          - Contents (Folder 2)
          - Nos. 1100-1199 (Folder 3)
          - Nos. 1200-1338 (Folder 4)
      - Speeches
        - 1940
          - Angers (Folder 5)
          - London (Folder 6)
        - 1941 (Folder 7)
        - 1942 (Folder 8)
        - 1943 (Folder 9)
        - 1944 (Folder 10)
    - Deputy Chairman
      - 1939 (Folder 11)
      - 1940
        - General (Folder 12)
        - Post-war Central Europe (Folder 13)
    - Komisje (Commissions)
      - Badan Przyczyn Kleski w 1939 Roku. Komisja Powolana w Zwiazku z Wynikiem Kampanii Wojennej 1939 roku (Commission for Investigation of the Causes of Defeat in 1939)
        - General
          - General, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 1)
          - Decrees, 1940 (Folder 2)
          - Reports
            - General, 1940-1941 (Folder 3)
            - "Lotnictwo Polskie" (Polish Airforce) by Tadeusz Cyprian, 1942
              - Part 1 (Folder 4)
              - Part 2 (Folder 5)
              - Part 3 (Folder 6)
              - Part 4 (Folder 7)
              - Part 5 (Folder 8)
              - Part 6 (Folder 9)
        - Officers accused
          - List (Folder 10)
          - Profiles
            - A-D (Folder 11)
            - E-J (Folder 12)
            - K-L (Folder 13)
            - M-O (Folder 14)
            - P-R (Folder 15)
            - S-T (Folder 16)
            - U-Z (Folder 17)
      - Budzetowa (Budget)
        - 1940
          - April (Box 62, Folder 1)
          - May (Folder 2)
          - June (Folder 3)
        - 1944 (Folder 4)
      - Budzetowo-Gospodarcza (Budget and Economy)
        - 1940 October (Folder 5)
        - 1942 (Folder 6)
        - 1943
          - February (Folder 7)
          - March (Folder 8)
      - Emigracyjna (Emigration), 1940-1941 (Folder 9)
      - Prawno-Konstytucyjna (Legal-Constitutional), 1941 (Folder 10)
      - Prawno-Polityczna (Legal-Political), 1945 (Folder 11)
      - Spoleczno-Gospodarcza (Socio-Economic)
        - 1942 (Folder 12)
        - 1943 (Folder 13)
        - 1944 (Folder 14)
        - 1945 (Folder 15)
      - Spraw Zagranicznych (Foreign Affairs)
        - 1942 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - 1943 (Folder 2)
        - 1944 (Folder 3)
        - 1945 (Folder 4)
      - Wojskowa (Military)
        - 1941 (Folder 5)
        - 1942 (Folder 6)
        - 1943 (Folder 7)
        - 1944 (Folder 8)
  - Wicepremier [Deputy Prime Minister]. See also Premier
    - General
      - General, 1942
        - January-June (Folder 9)
        - July-December (Folder 10)
      - Correspondence
        - 1941
          - April-August (Folder 11)
          - September-October (Folder 12)
          - November-December (Folder 13)
        - 1942
          - March-April (Folder 14)
          - May-August (Folder 15)
          - September-December (Folder 16)
        - 1943
          - January-February (Folder 17)
          - March-April (Folder 18)
          - May-June (Folder 19)
      - Reports
        - Great Britain. House of Commons. Questions concerning Poland, 1942-1943 (Folder 20)
        - Polish-Czechoslovak relations
          - Czech internal politics (Box 64, Folder 1)
          - Recognition of Edvard Benes as President (Folder 2)
          - Slask Cieszynski (Folder 3)
        - Post-war agricultural reconstruction, 1942 (Folder 4)
      - Transcripts of talks
        - General
          - Contents (Folder 5)
          - Andrews, Henry (Folder 6)
          - Arciszewski, Tomasz - Mikolajczyk, Stanislaw, 1945 (Folder 7)
          - Bogomolov, Ambassador (Folder 8)
          - Churchill, Winston, 1943 July 8 (Folder 9)
          - East European Peasant Movement Leaders, 1941 September 24 (Folder 10)
          - Gammans, Captain, 1942 October 13 (Folder 11)
          - Gavrilovic, 1942 January 9 (Folder 12)
          - Hodzha, Milan, 1941 September 6 (Folder 13)
          - Raczynski, Ambassador, on Winston Churchill, 1943 (Folder 14)
          - July 6
          - Ripka and Heirath, 1941 September 23 (Folder 15)
          - Rucart, Marc, 1943 October 18 (Folder 16)
          - Sikorski, Wladyslaw
            - Materials, 1942 (Folder 17)
            - Notes